Iwamoto Yuki

Senior Full-Stack Web and Blockchain Developer

CONTACT

- Address: 2931 Dufferin St, Toronto, Ontario, Canada

- Git: https://github.com/Cheetah0723

- Mail: <u>iyuki723@gmail.com</u>,

- Skype: live:.cid.93557e1a3c22ca1a

- Discord: !.Yuki0723#0158

- Phone: +1 832 932 7100

SUMMARY

I am Iwamoto Yuki from Canada!

As a senior full-stack web and blockchain developer, I have 8+ years of experience.

I graduated from Kyoto University in Japan, and while I was studying in university, I was most interested in computer science and mathematics because I loved computers and logical problems.

So, to become a software engineer, I studied developing languages like C/C#, Python, and Java very hard.

In those days, I was interested in ML and Image processing so I started to research these areas.

After graduating from university, I had joined in VMO company in Japan with my IT talent.

In this company, I had PHP/Laravel and JavaScript projects and had studied web development.

After a year, with my talent and strong logic, I became a senior full-stack developer and since then I have started to develop entire websites.

Many companies have hired me for my amazing skills, where I have contributed to the company's performance by producing great results using React, Vue, Node, Laravel, Django and etc.

Of course, I mastered almost all of the JavaScript library and frameworks and my major stacks are MERN and MEVN.

Nowadays, science and technology have been developing very fast and blockchain is one of the most important and professional areas of computer science.

Since I was interested in Blockchain, I have researched very hard and now, I like and love blockchain development.

I always strive to become a world-class developer, and it is my dream to become the best developer.

There is a principle I found while developing the program.

- Respect clients and follow their wishes.
- ➤ Until you value yourself, you won't value your time. Until you value your time, you will not do anything with it.
- ➤ Pixel perfect, structured, and optimized design, smart and clean coding.

I always work with this principle and strive to upload this principle.

Thank you for your attention.

EDUCATION

- Bachelor of Science in Software Development and Master of Mathematics.

Kyoto University,

Yoshidahonmachi, Sakyo Ward, Kyoto, 606-8501, Japan,

2010 - 2013

- Relevant Coursework.

Operating Systems Architecture, Linux/Unix Programming, Usability in Website and Software Design, C++ Programming I & II, Web Page

Development, Relational Database Design & SQL, Data Engineering, Advanced Software Programming.

SKILLS

Main Skills:

React, Next, Vue, Nuxt, Node, Nest, Wordpress, Python, Django, PHP, Laravel, Solidity, Web3, C/C#, Java

Mastered programming language:

JavaScript / TypeScript / Python / Java / C / C#

Frontend development:

- Development language:
 JavaScript, Wordpress, TypeScript, React / Redux, Vue / Vuex, Next,
 Nuxt, Three.js and WebGL
- UI Framework:
 Bootstrap, Ant Design, Material UI / Kit, React Bootstrap
- CSS, Sass, Less for style

Backend development:

- Development language:
 Node, Express, Django, Asp.net, PHP, Laravel
- Database development:
 MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MSSQL

- Other development:

- Git, Git Flow for version control
- Understanding of different types of testing (Unit / Integration / Functional)
- WebSocket, Socket.io, Storage, Notifications
- AWS cloud service / Aws lambda / Azure / API gateway, Amplify,
 Cognito REST API
- Payment integration for Paypal and Stripe
- Mail notification using several frameworks

- Blockchain development:

• Language: Solidity, Rust

• Token: ERC20, ERC721, ERC1155

• Swap: like Uniswap, Sushiswap, Pancakeswap

• Platforms: Ethereum, Tron, Solana, Algorand

WORK EXPERIENCE

Blockchain developer.

Freelancer, September 2019 - Now

- Developed Dapp using React / Redux / Redux-Saga / React Hooks / Web3, Ether.js and IPFS.
- Familiar with NFT projects such as NFT minting Dapp, NFT marketplace, Swap, and Farming.
- Implement authentication based on IPFS with Moralis for NFT product.
- Handling with DeFi exchange projects using Pancakeswap, Uniswap, Sushiswap and More.
- DEX and Centralized Crypto Exchange, Yield Farming, Liquidity Mining Protocols.
- Using the solidity framework features, optimized the smart contract program and boosted performance by 20%.
- Smart Green Bonds includes an ecological state protocol that connects IoT off-chain data to Smart Contracts on Ethereum.

Full-stack developer.

INTERSOG, January 2018 – September 2019 &

NRI, an IT managed services company, July 2016 – January 2018

- Implemented pixel perfect frontend by design of client.
- Built websites using React & Django.
- 3d animation effect websites using Three.js and WebGL.
- Implemented SEO (Search Engine Optimization) to existing websites.
- Retrieved data from multiple, different storage APIs, using GraphQL,

- Payment Integration.
- Implemented Chat bot integration to several websites.
- Completed Online game using Unity and Node.js and Websocket.
- Made online game (Poker) using Laravel Livewire and Vue.js.
- Web Hosting to AWS / Cpanel.
- Built Websites using React, Redux, Django, DynamoDB.
- Used ASP.NET Core and Python Flask and Java.
- Developed an internal application that tracked the life of an order through a windows service and MongoDB.
- Used GraphQL and REST API
- Development of Electron App and Used Next.js and Nuxt.js Web Hosting to AWS / Azure.

Backend Developer.

VMO JAPAN, March 2015 - July 2016

- Developed automated software which manages infrastructure without human intervention.
- Built multiple language website using Laravel with Vue.js frontend developer.
- Built shopping website using Django with React.
- Implemented SEO(Search Engine Optimization) for several websites.
- Paypal integration using Laravel and Node.js.
- Web Scrapping using Python.
- Web Hosting to Azure / CWP.

Frontend Developer.

PressPly US, March 2022 - Recent

- Role:
 - Head Frontend Developer
- Task:
 - Part time development

VMO JAPAN, April 2014 – March 2015

- Implemented Single Page Application architecture and client side MVC using AngularJS.
- Used Bootstrap features such as Model objects, Tabs, Tooltips, Carousals throughout the application.
- Used Angular UI Grid directives such as filters, rootscope, childscope, modal, and template, etc.
- Implemented components and wire-frames using cross-browser compatible CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and Ajax, Angular JS.
- Used ng-view directive to refresh only certain section of the page and reduce the load on the web server.

Implemented websites suing Laravel Blade and Bootstrap and JavaScript and CSS.

TYPICAL PROJECTS

- **Mooningmonkey-NFT** (https://mooningmonkey.com/)

My role in this project was smart contract and web3 frontend.

Also, I was charge in developing art generation.

This is NFT minting website.

Releasing 1000 NFTs for monkey-animals.

Frontend was developed by react and web3.js.

- **Quidverse-NFT** (https://quidverse.com/)

My client Quidverse wanted to me make minting site from her design with pixel perfect and fully responsible.

To complete this site, I had worked for 7 days without sleeping.

Finally, I had completed this site and deployed it on his time.

About this project, I used Next for frontend, Web3.js for wallet integration, and Solidity for smart contracts.

- **Lotusvancouver** (https://lotusvancouver.com)

Lotus Vancouver, car company in Canada wanted our IT company to make their car site using Next.js and Node.js.

This was a very large site to complete it only myself.

In fact, in that time, our company was busy to solve many problems from clients, so I was charge in all this project.

This site is a posting site and many people are using this site and buy and rent several type of cars.

This site's structure is organized that front is React, backend is Node and DB is MongoDB.

I had used Material UI and Bootstrap, so it is responsive site.

- **Onzo** (https://onzo.co.jp)

The Onzo business wanted to make this site, which was equipment shop site that they had made.

They wanted to build his shopping site using Next.js and Node.js with my creative idea from scratch.

Of course, I had made this site in pixel perfect.

I took part in building frontend and backend developments.

In fact, it was difficult to build all this site myself but I tried and finally finished perfectly.

Now, Onzo business is making more profit from this shopping site.

- **Porcelain Superstore** (https://www.porcelainsuperstore.co.uk)

This site is shopping site about beautiful wall tiles.

This site was developed with a team, which has 10 members: designer, admin dashboard developer, client side developer, backend developer and etc.

I was in charge of frontend development and in here I used React.

- **Hotel-spider** (https://www.hotel-spider.com/en)

This is my first project after graduating.

In fact, then I had no experience with web developing so it looked like little not good.

In our company, they wanted to made this site only myself.

I tried to make this site with myself but it was really difficult.

I made this site using Laravel and GSAP.

Language

- English (Fluent, Advanced speaking)
- Japanese (Native)
- Chinese (Middle, Advanced reading and writing)

Certification

- **HackerRank** (December 24, 2021)

C/C++ certification,
Python certification,
Node (Javascript) certification,
React Certification

Training Courses

- Full Stack React & Redux & Node (March 23, 2016)

I learned advantages of MERN stack and I mastered how to make perfect project with MERN stack.

- **Master Laravel with Vue.js Full stack development** (November 23, 2017) Through this course, I mastered Laravel and Vue and I had high ability what can build wonderful Laravel & Vue projects.
- **CryptoZombie** (July 23, 2019)

I learned how to make smart contracts using solidity for developing simple crypto games.

- **Svelte.dev** (September 11, 2021)

I learned Svelte tutorial for developing svelte project. In my opinion, nowadays Svelte is the most advantage developing language.